Solon, Ohio. Solon Community Church records, 1897-2022.
Congregational Library & Archives
Solon, Ohio. Solon Community Church records, 1897-2022.
RG5460
Congregational Library & Archives
8.47 Cubic Feet
(9 boxes, 3 flat files)
The Solon Community Church was founded in 1834 as a congregational fellowship before joining the Cleveland Presbytery in 1840. The church burned down in 1897 and held services at the schoolhouse and Disciples of Christ church until a new building was dedicated in 1898. The Solon Presbyterian and Disciples churches joined to form the Solon Federated Church in 1922 which changed its name to the Solon Community Church in 1948, and which split apart in 1951. In 1955, the church rejoined the congregational denomination by joining the Congregational Christian Conference and later the United Church of Christ in 1961. To keep up with the growing city, a new church was built in 1960 with various renovations occurring in the following years. Due to declining membership, the Solon Community Church permanently closed in 2022 with the last service held in November of that year. This collection includes records documenting the history, activities, and members of the Solon Community Church through meeting minutes, reports, financial and legal records, member records, newsletters, photographs, church histories, programs, and pamphlets.
Solon Community Church (Solon, Ohio.)
Solon Federated Church (Solon, Ohio.)
Restrictions on Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted and open to the public.
Acquisition Information
Materials were donated to the Congregational Library & Archives by Solon Community Church in May 2023 and June 2024; 2023-32 and 2024-20.
Historical Note
The Solon Community Church was founded in 1834 in Solon, Ohio, as a "fellowship of Christians in a Congregational manner" by a group of men led by Rev. John Steward. In 1836, a church building was raised and dedicated, and the first minister was called. Due to financial difficulties in the first decade, the church was unable to be self-supporting and in 1840, it was taken under the care of the Cleveland Presbytery and their Home Missions Board. The church became fully Presbyterian in 1871. In 1841, some families within the church separated to found the Disciples of Christ church nearby. In 1853, the church enlarged their meeting house and in 1897, the church building burned to the ground. While the new building was being built, the congregation held services in the schoolhouse and the Disciple church which later burned down in 1899. The new church building broke ground in 1897, laid the cornerstone in September 1897 and was dedicated in January 1898.
In 1922, the Solon Presbyterian church and the Disciple church formed a federation to become the Solon Federated Church with services alternating between the two church buildings until eventually the entirety of services were held in the Presbyterian church. In 1924, a parsonage was built next to the Presbyterian church. Since the church served the entire Protestant community in Solon, the church changed its name to the Solon Community Church in 1948. Shortly after, in 1951, some of the members of the Disciple church decided to reform their own church and refurbished their church building which became the Pioneer Memorial Church in 1953. Also in 1953, Solon Community Church was forced to buy back their building and parsonage from the Cleveland Presbytery after a court trial regarding the question of ownership. In 1955, the church returned to the congregational denomination by joining the Congregational Christian Conference and in 1961, joined the United Church of Christ formed from the merger of the Congregational Christian and Evangelical and Reformed churches.
To keep up with the growth of Solon, the church purchased land in 1957 for a new building and broke ground in 1960 with the cornerstone laid in September 1960, and a dedication in April 1961. In 1962, a parsonage was purchased on Linden Dr. and was later replaced by a parsonage on Copley Ave in 1972. The Copley Ave parsonage was sold in 1983 to the then minister Rev. Mark Thomas. Over the years, various renovations and building improvements occurred, notably in 1975, 1995-1997, 2003 with the new Congregational Life Center which was dedicated in January 2006, and 2007. As the church entered the 2020s, membership declined until the church decided to permanently close in 2022 with the last service held in November 2022.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains records documenting the history, activities and members of Solon Community Church in Solon, Ohio. The records include council meeting minutes, board meeting minutes, annual reports, financial records, legal records, site plans, membership cards, church registers, vital statistics, service programs, pamphlets, brochures, photographs, photo slides, church histories, and newsletters.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six series, three of which have been further arranged into subseries. Materials have been arranged chronologically by start date within the series and subseries with materials of similar topics grouped together.
Series 1: Church Council records, 1958-2022
Series 2: Church Boards, 1934-2022
Subseries 1: Board of Trustees, 1932-2020
Subseries 2: Board of Benevolence, 1967-2021
Subseries 3: Board of Deacons, 1946-2022
Subseries 4: Women's Fellowship, 1948-1972
Subseries 5: Board of Elders, 1936-2002
Subseries 6: Board of Christian Education, 1962-2019
Subseries 7: Ladies Auxillary, 1959-1978
Subseries 8: Rebecca Circle, 1970-1985
Subseries 9: Naomi Circle, 1956-1979
Subseries 10: Esther Circle, 1953-2000
Subseries 11: King's Men Fellowship, 1957-1962
Subseries 12: Board of Stewards, 1961-1966
Subseries 13: All Boards Meetings, 1988-2016
Series 3: Membership records, 1923-2022
Series 4: Administrative records, 1951-2022
Subseries 1: Annual Reports, 1956-2022
Subseries 2: Renovations, 1957-2007
Series 5: Church history, 1897-2022
Subseries 1: Photographs, 1958-2002
Series 6: "The Light" newsletter, 1953-2017
Related Materials
Additional records related to the history of Solon Community Church prior to 1955 when it was a Presbyterian church can be found at the Presbyterian Historical Society in Solon Community Church (Solon, Ohio) records, accession number 23 0614.
Church architecture -- Designs and plans.; Church finance.; Church records and registers.; Church membership.; Church newsletters.; Church societies.; Federated churches; Women -- Religious life.; Solon Community Church (Solon, Ohio.); Solon Federated Church (Solon, Ohio.); First Presbyterian Church (Solon, Ohio.)
- Church Council records, 1958 2022; 1958-2022
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the records of the Solon Community Church council including meeting minutes from the council, some meeting minutes from the church boards, supporting documents relating to the council, and records from the council's executive committee.
  - Council Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Council Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Council Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Council Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Council Minutes, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Council Minutes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Council Minutes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Council Minutes, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Council Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Council Minutes, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Council Minutes, 1988 1989; 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Council Minutes, 1990 1992; 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Council Minutes, 1993 1995; 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Council Minutes, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Council Minutes, 2005 2006; 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Council Minutes, 2007 2008; 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Council Minutes, 2009 2010; 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Council Minutes, 2011 2012; 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Council Minutes, 2013 2015; 2013-2015 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Council Minutes, 2016 2018; 2016-2018 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Council Minutes, 2019 2022; 2019-2022 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Council Minutes, 1958 (Box 2, File 1)
  - Council Minutes, 1958 1959; 1958-19559 (Box 2, File 2)
  - Council Minutes, 1959 1960; 1959-1960 (Box 2, File 3)
  - Council Minutes, 1961 (Box 2, File 4)
  - Council Minutes, 1962 (Box 2, File 5)
  - Council Minutes, 1963 1964; 1963-1964 (Box 2, File 6)
  - Council Minutes, 1965 (Box 2, File 7)
  - Council Minutes, 1966 (Box 2, File 8)
  - Council Minutes, 1967 1969; 1967-1969 (Box 2, File 9)
  - Council Minutes, 1971 1973; 1971-1973 (Box 2, File 10)
  - Council Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, File 11)
  - Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 2, File 12)
  - Council Minutes, 1985 (Box 2, File 13)
  - Council Minutes, 1996 2000; 1996-2000 (Box 2, File 14)
  - Council Executive Committee, 1982 1984; 1982-1984 (Box 2, File 15)
- Church Boards, 1934 2022; 1934-2022
  This series contains records from various church boards and groups including meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, member lists, brochures, pamphlets, cards, ledgers, and other documents relating to the work of the boards.
  - Board of Trustees, 1932 2020; 1932-2020
    This series contains records from the Board of Trustees, formerly known as the Executive Board prior to 1948 when the Solon Community Church split from the Solon Federated Church. The series contains meeting minutes, annual reports, budgets, rental agreements, contracts, and other documents relating to the trustees.
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1932 1936; 1932-1936 (Box 3, File 9)
    - Executive Board Minutes, 1936 1947; 1936-1947 (Box 3, File 10)
    - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1948 1956; 1948-1956 (Box 3, File 11)
    - Trustees Minutes, 1985 1988; 1985-1988 (Box 3, File 12)
    - Trustees Minutes, 1994 2000; 1994-2000 (Box 3, File 13)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2004 2005; 2004-2005 (Box 3, File 14)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2006 (Box 3, File 15)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2007 2010; 2007-2010 (Box 3, File 16)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2012 2014; 2012-2014 (Box 3, File 17)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2015 2018; 2015-2018 (Box 3, File 18)
    - Trustees Minutes, 2019 2020; 2019-2020 (Box 3, File 19)
    - Board of Trustees, 1953 1955; 1953-1955 (Box 3, File 20)
    - Board of Trustees, 2003 2005; 2003-2005 (Box 3, File 21)
    - Board of Trustees, 2006 2007; 2006-2007 (Box 3, File 22)
    - Board of Trustees miscellaneous, 2007 2009; 2007-2009 (Box 3, File 23)
    - Board of Trustees, 2008 2009; 2008-2009 (Box 3, File 24)
    - Trustees Minutes, 1976 1980; 1976-1980 (Box 5, File 5)
  - Board of Benevolence, 1967 2021; 1967-2021
    This series contains records from the board of benevolence including meeting minutes, budgets, and other records relating to the board.
    - Benevolence Board Minutes, 1967 1974; 1967-1974 (Box 3, File 6)
    - Benevolence Board Minutes, 1994 1999; 1994-1999 (Box 3, File 7)
    - Board of Benevolence Minutes, 2009 2021; 2009-2021 (Box 3, File 8)
  - Board of Deacons, 1962 2022; 1946-2022
    This series contains records from the board of deacons, also known as the diaconate, including meeting minutes and supporting documents from their meetings.
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1971 1973; 1971-1973 (Box 4, File 2)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1989 1990; 1989-1990 (Box 4, File 3)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1993 2000; 1993-2000 (Box 4, File 4)
    - Diaconate Minutes, 2004 2007; 2004-2007 (Box 4, File 5)
    - Diaconate Minutes, 2008 2011; 2008-2011 (Box 4, File 6)
    - Diaconate Minutes, 2012 2015; 2012-2015 (Box 4, File 7)
    - Diaconate Minutes, 2016 2017; 2016-2017 (Box 4, File 8)
    - Diaconate Minutes, 2018 2022; 2018-2022 (Box 4, File 9)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1962 1965; 1962-1965 (Box 5, File 2)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1968 1970; 1968-1970 (Box 5, File 3)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1983 1988; 1983-1988 (Box 5, File 4)
  - Women's Fellowship, 1948 1972; 1948-1972
    This series contains records from the Women's Fellowship group including meeting minutes, thank you notes, constitutions, pamphlets, and other documents relating to the fellowship.
    - Women's Fellowship, 1948 1968; 1948-1968 (Box 4, File 10)
    - Women's Fellowship Minutes, 1957 1963; 1957-1963 (Box 4, File 11)
    - Women's Fellowship Minutes, 1964 1966; 1964-1966 (Box 4, File 12)
    - Women's Fellowship Thank You Notes, 1969 1971; 1969-1971 (Box 4, File 13)
    - Women's Fellowship MInutes, 1967 1968; 1967-1968 (Box 5, File 11)
    - Women's Fellowship Minutes, 1969 1972; 1969-1972 (Box 5, File 12)
  - Board of Elders, 1950 2022; 1936-2002
    This series contains records from the Board of Elders including meeting minutes, member lists, and other documents relating to the board.
    - Board of Elders, 1950 2022; 1950-2022 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Board of Elders Minutes, 1975 2002; 1975-2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Board of Elders Minutes, 2004 2007; 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1962 2019; 1962-2019
    This series contains records from the Board of Christian Education including meeting minutes, member lists, booklets, job descriptions, budgets, and other documents relating to christian education.
    - Board of Christian Education Miscellaneous, 1962 1972; 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Christian Education Minutes, 1994 2019; 1994-2019 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Board of Christian Education, 1964 1966; 1964-1966 (Box 5, File 9)
    - Board of Christian Education Minutes, 1967 1973; 1967-1973 (Box 5, File 10)
  - Ladies Auxiliary, 1959 1978; 1959-1978
    This series contains records from the Ladies Auxiliary group including meeting minutes and related documents in two ledgers.
    - Ladies Auxiliary Minutes, 1959 1967; 1959-1967 (Box 5, File 7)
    - Ladies Auxiliary Minutes, 1967 1978; 1967-1978 (Box 5, File 8)
  - All Boards Meetings, 1988 2016; 1988-2016
    This series contains records from the monthly all boards meetings which occasionally overlapped with the church council meetings. The series includes meeting minutes and documents related to the meetings.
    - All Boards Meetings, 2004 2016; 2004-2016 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Monthly Board Minutes, 1958 1993; 1958-1993 (Box 5, File 6)
  - Rebecca Circle, 1970 1985; 1970-1985
    This series contains records from the Rebecca Circle, one of the women's circles, and includes meeting minutes, financial reports, and other documents relating to the circle.
    - Rebecca Circle, 1970 1985; 1970-1985 (Box 3, File 5)
  - Naomi Circle, 1956 1979; 1956-1979
    This series contains records from the Naomi Circle, one of the women's circles, and includes meeting minutes and other documents from the circle.
    - Naomi Circle Minutes, 1956 1967; 1956-1967 (Box 3, File 1)
    - Naomi Circle Minutes, 1968 1979; 1968-1979 (Box 3, File 2)
  - Esther Circle, 1953 2000; 1953-2000
    This series contains records from the Esther Circle, one of the women's circles, which was formerly known as the Big Sisters group until October 1960. The series includes meeting minutes, and other documents relating to the circle.
    - Esther Circle, 1953 1966; 1953-1966 (Box 3, File 3)
    - Esther Circle, 1980 2000; 1980-2000 (Box 3, File 4)
  - King's Men Fellowship, 1957 1962; 1957-1962
    This series contains records from the King's Men Fellowship and includes constitutions and correspondence.
    - King's Men Fellowship, 1957 1962; 1957-1962 (Box 4, File 1)
  - Board of Stewards, 1961 1966; 1961-1966
    This series contains records from the Board of Stewards and includes meeting minutes, annual reports, financial reports, and other documents relating to the board.
    - Board of Stewards, 1961 1966; 1961-1966 (Box 5, File 1)
- Membership records, 1923 2022; 1923-2022
  This series contains vital statistic records relating to the members of Solon Community Church. The series contains membership cards, two church registers, member directories, member transfer records, marriage certificates and records, baptismal records, and member and officer lists.
  - Church Register, 1923 1955; 1923-1955 (Box 4, File 14)
  - Church Register, 1957 1996; 1957-1996 (Box 4, File 15)
  - Member Records, 1969 1980; 1969-1980 (Box 4, File 16)
  - Marriages, 1972 2022; 1972-2022 (Box 4, File 17)
  - Baptismal Records, 1937 2018; 1937-2018 (Box 4, File 18)
  - Membership Directory, 1958 (Box 4, File 19)
  - Directories, 1981 1998; 1981-1998 (Box 4, File 20)
  - Directories, 2000 2018; 2000-2018 (Box 4, File 21)
  - Directory Update, 2008 (Box 4, File 22)
  - Membership Transfers, 1938 2020; 1938-2020 (Box 4, File 23)
  - Membership Transfers, 1943 2020; 1943-2020 (Box 4, File 24)
  - Membership Transfers, 1945 1985; 1945-1985 (Box 4, File 25)
  - Membership Transfers, 1946 1984; 1946-1984 (Box 4, File 26)
  - Membership Transfers, 1955 1985; 1955-1985 (Box 4, File 27)
  - Membership Transfers, 1985 2020; 1985-2020 (Box 4, File 28)
  - Memberships, 1962 2006; 1962-2006 (Box 5, File 13)
  - Officer and Member Lists, 1973 1993; 1973-1993 (Box 5, File 14)
  - Membership Cards, 1936 1995; 1936-1995 (Box 9)
- Administrative records, 1951 2022; 1951-2022
  This series contains records relating to the administration of Solon Community Church. The series includes legal records, financial records, employment documents, congregational meeting minutes, annual reports, committee records, inventories, renovation and property records, site plans, constitutions, and attendance records.
  - Annual reports, 1956 2022; 1956-2022
    This series contains annual reports for the church.
    - Annual Reports, 1956 1958; 1956-1958 (Box 6, File 26)
    - Annual Reports, 1959 1962; 1959-1962 (Box 6, File 27)
    - Annual Reports, 1962 1964; 1962-1964 (Box 6, File 28)
    - Annual Reports, 1965 1969; 1965-1969 (Box 6, File 29)
    - Annual Reports, 1970 1974; 1970-1974 (Box 6, File 30)
    - Annual Reports, 1975 1979; 1975-1979 (Box 6, File 31)
    - Annual Reports, 1980 1984; 1980-1984 (Box 6, File 32)
    - Annual Reports, 1985 1989; 1985-1989 (Box 6, File 33)
    - Annual Reports, 1990 1994; 1990-1994 (Box 6, File 34)
    - Annual Reports, 1995 1999; 1995-1999 (Box 6, File 35)
    - Annual Reports, 2000 2004; 2000-2004 (Box 6, File 36)
    - Annual Reports, 2005 2009; 2005-2009 (Box 6, File 37)
    - Annual Reports, 2010 2014; 2010-2014 (Box 6, File 38)
    - Annual Reports, 2015 2019; 2015-2019 (Box 6, File 39)
    - Annual Reports, 2020 2022; 2020-2022 (Box 6, File 40)
  - Renovations, 1957 2007; 1957-2007
    This series contains records about renovations done at Solon Community Church and includes site plans, budgets, meeting minutes, canvass records, pamphlets, correspondence, and other documents related to the renovations.
    - 2007 Renovation (Box 6, File 20)
    - Congregational Life Center, 2002 2003; 2002-2003 (Box 6, File 19)
    - Project 2000 Minutes, 1995 1997; 1995-1997 (Box 6, File 18)
    - 1975 Renovation, 1974 1975; 1974-1975 (Box 6, File 17)
    - Capital Improvements Committee MInutes, 1987 (Box 6, File 16)
    - Building Fund Canvass, 1957 (Box 6, File 15)
    - Site Plans, 1957 2003; 1957-2003 (Folder 7)
    - Site Plans, 1984 2003; 1984-2003 (Folder 6)
    - Site Plans, 2003 (Folder 1)
  - Fund Raising Agreements, 1957 1960; 1957-1960 (Box 5, File 15)
  - Financial Reports, 1956 1996; 1956-1996 (Box 5, File 16)
  - Memorial Fund, 1970 2013; 1970-2013 (Box 5, File 17)
  - Sunday School Roster, 1985 1993; 1985-1993 (Box 5, File 18)
  - Employment Contracts, 1952 (Box 5, File 19)
  - Kruse Memorial Garden, 1982 1991; 1982-1991 (Box 5, File 20)
  - Building Fund, 1954 1957; 1954-1957 (Box 5, File 21)
  - Property Records, 1956 1983; 1956-1983 (Box 5, File 22)
  - Building Use Register, 1962 1967; 1962-1967 (Box 5, File 23)
  - Legal Records, 1951 2004; 1951-2004 (Box 5, File 24)
  - Scout Hall Disposition, 1956 1959; 1956-1959 (Box 5, File 25)
  - Linden Dr Parsonage, 1962 (Box 5, File 26)
  - Copley Ave Parsonage, 1972 1987; 1972-1987 (Box 5, File 27)
  - Congregational Meeting Minutes, 1980 2022; 1980-2022 (Box 5, File 29)
  - Congregational Meeting Minutes, 1954 1979; 1954-1979 (Box 5, File 28)
  - Constitutions, 1953 2017; 1953-2017 (Box 6, File 1)
  - Constitutions, 1941 2022; 1941-2022 (Box 6, File 2)
  - Stewardship Report, 2007 (Box 6, File 3)
  - Building Committee, 1960 (Box 6, File 4)
  - Music Committee, 1968 2004; 1968-2004 (Box 6, File 5)
  - Altar Committee, 1981 (Box 6, File 6)
  - New Horizons Team Meetings, 2019 2020; 2019-2020 (Box 6, File 7)
  - Funeral Receptions, 1995 1996; 1995-1996 (Box 6, File 8)
  - Pastoral Call, 1981 2021; 1981-2021 (Box 6, File 9)
  - Pastoral Search Committee, 2010 (Box 6, File 10)
  - Inventories, 1953 2013; 1953-2013 (Box 6, File 11)
  - Memorial Gifts, 1960 2005; 1960-2005 (Box 6, File 12)
  - Financial Reports, 1968 1978; 1968-1978 (Box 6, File 13)
  - Financial Audits, 1986 2007; 1986-2007 (Box 6, File 14)
  - Property Appraisal and Renovation, 1954 1977; 1954-1977 (Box 6, File 21)
  - Property Reports, 1990 2015; 1990-2015 (Box 6, File 22)
  - Church Profile, 1978 2013; 1978-2013 (Box 6, File 23)
  - Usher Attendance Records, 2011 2022; 2011-2022 (Box 6, File 24)
  - Clerk Reports, 1981 2021; 1981-2021 (Box 6, File 25)
- Church history, 1897 2022; 1897-2022
  This series contains records about the history of the Solon Community Church, formerly the Solon Federated Church. The series contains written histories, church services, photos, news articles, organizational outlines, brochures, obituaries, funeral booklets. and records and correspondence relating to special events or services.
  - Photographs, 1958 2002; 1958-2002
    This series contains photos depicting the church and its members, and includes polaroids, photo slides, and photographs. Some of the photos are undated.
    - Slides, 1958 1971; 1958-1971 (Box 7, File 11)
    - Polaroids and Photographs, undated (Box 7, File 12)
    - Photos, 2001 2002; 2001-2002 (Box 7, File 13)
    - Sunday School Photos, 1999 2001; 1999-2001 (Box 7, File 14)
    - Family Sunday, 2001 (Box 7, File 15)
  - Church History, 1897 2009; 1897-2009 (Box 5, File 30)
  - Church Organization, 1958 2005; 1958-2005 (Box 5, File 31)
  - Dedication Tenth Anniversary, 1971 (Box 5, File 32)
  - Publicity, 1960 2013; 1960-2013 (Box 5, File 33)
  - Leadership Seminar, 1975 (Box 7, File 1)
  - Funerals, 1991 2020; 1991-2020 (Box 7, File 2)
  - In Memoriam book, 1991 2016; 1991-2016 (Box 7, File 3)
  - Intallation Services, 1962 2011; 1962-2011 (Box 7, File 4)
  - Dedication, 1961 (Box 7, File 5)
  - Mortage Burning, 1973 (Box 7, File 6)
  - 150th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 7, File 7)
  - 175th Anniversary, 2009 (Box 7, File 8)
  - Welcome Brochures, 1962 2019; 1962-2019 (Box 7, File 9)
  - Open and Affirming Coalition, 2019 (Box 7, File 10)
  - Church Services, 1929 1996; 1929-1996 (Box 8, File 19)
- "The Light" newsletter, 1953 2017; 1953-2017
  This series contains the church newsletter, "The Light", which was printed on a regular weekly, monthly, or seasonal basis depending on the year. The years 1966-1980 are missing from the collection.
  - "Light", 1953 1954; 1953-1954 (Box 7, File 16)
  - "Light", 1955 (Box 7, File 17)
  - "Light", 1956 (Box 7, File 18)
  - "Light", 1957 (Box 7, File 19)
  - "Light", 1958 1958; 1958-1959 (Box 7, File 20)
  - "Light", 1996 1997; 1996-1997 (Box 7, File 21)
  - "Light", 1999 (Box 7, File 22)
  - "Light", 2000 (Box 7, File 23)
  - "Light", 2001 (Box 7, File 24)
  - "Light", 2002 (Box 7, File 25)
  - "Light", 2003 (Box 7, File 26)
  - "Light", 2004 (Box 7, File 27)
  - "Light", 2005 (Box 7, File 28)
  - "Light", 2006 (Box 7, File 29)
  - "Light", 2007 (Box 7, File 30)
  - "Light", 2008 (Box 7, File 31)
  - "Light", 2009 (Box 7, File 32)
  - "Light", 2010 (Box 7, File 33)
  - "Light", 2011 (Box 7, File 34)
  - "Light", 2012 (Box 7, File 35)
  - "Light", 2013 (Box 7, File 36)
  - "Light", 2014 (Box 7, File 37)
  - "Light", 2015 (Box 7, File 38)
  - "Light", 2016 (Box 7, File 39)